{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "eu", "answer": "sou" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "és" },
    { "prompt": "ele", "answer": "é" },
    { "prompt": "ela", "answer": "é" },
    { "prompt": "sou", "answer": "eu" },
    { "prompt": "és", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "é", "answer": "ele/ela" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "eu", "answer": "tenho" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "tens" },
    { "prompt": "ele", "answer": "tem" },
    { "prompt": "ela", "answer": "tem" },
    { "prompt": "tenho", "answer": "eu" },
    { "prompt": "tens", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "tem", "answer": "ele/ela" }
  ]
}
